<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journey on kortni.ca</title>
    <link>https://kortni.ca/categories/journey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journey on kortni.ca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kortni.ca/categories/journey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year With No Beer</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/year-no-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/year-no-beer/</guid>
      <description>The last sip of beer I had was Oct 7th, 2019.
It has been one year since that date and now&amp;hellip;
My liver is thanking me.
I&amp;rsquo;ve regretted our investment in our friend&amp;rsquo;s local Brewery on more than one occasion. Especially when they released a couple new beer that almost broke me. The berry sours. Ohhh gawd the berry sours.
I needed to spend some sober time away from the bottle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned From Shaving My Head</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/shaved-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/shaved-head/</guid>
      <description>With blonde curly hair halfway down my back, one day I put it in a few pigtails, and cut them all off. My girlfriend was about to lose her hair so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d join her.
When I was growing up, I&amp;rsquo;d always said that I would shave my head if one of my friends got cancer. Based on the rate of cancer I&amp;rsquo;d seen, I felt like someone close to me was bound to get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saying Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/saying-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/saying-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>I love being on vacation when there&amp;rsquo;s no cell phone reception.
I do NOT like when cell reception becomes available and all the missed contact attempts flood onto my phone. It feels like everybody wants a piece of me, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even officially back yet! I suppose I don&amp;rsquo;t haave to turn my phone on until I return home. Hmmm perhaps.
Even when you know it&amp;rsquo;s coming, you&amp;rsquo;re never ready to hear the words that your friend has passed away.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>