<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on kortni.ca</title>
    <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on kortni.ca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kortni.ca/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Blankets</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/security-blankets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/security-blankets/</guid>
      <description>I was feeling victimmy about my messiness the other day as I noticed our clean house revert back to an untidy state.
I watched as our clean island in the kitchen seemed to slowly attract item after item to it&amp;rsquo;s surface until there was a familiar size mound of everyone&amp;rsquo;s crap. I wondered why this kept happening. Why was it so hard for me to keep things clean?
My husband puts his stuff away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staying Home for School</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/staying-home-for-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/staying-home-for-school/</guid>
      <description>Back to school this month looks a lot different for us.
We&amp;rsquo;re staying home for grade 3 and 5 and doing distanced learning through SIDES. I took some courses through SIDES when I was in high school and really enjoye it. I&amp;rsquo;m guessing my sons won&amp;rsquo;t have to paper snail mail their math work into their teachers for grading and wait weeks, instead of seconds, for the results of their tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year With No Beer</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/year-no-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/year-no-beer/</guid>
      <description>The last sip of beer I had was Oct 7th, 2019.
It has been one year since that date and now&amp;hellip;
My liver is thanking me.
I&amp;rsquo;ve regretted our investment in our friend&amp;rsquo;s local Brewery on more than one occasion. Especially when they released a couple new beer that almost broke me. The berry sours. Ohhh gawd the berry sours.
I needed to spend some sober time away from the bottle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned From Shaving My Head</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/shaved-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/shaved-head/</guid>
      <description>With blonde curly hair halfway down my back, one day I put it in a few pigtails, and cut them all off. My girlfriend was about to lose her hair so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d join her.
When I was growing up, I&amp;rsquo;d always said that I would shave my head if one of my friends got cancer. Based on the rate of cancer I&amp;rsquo;d seen, I felt like someone close to me was bound to get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go is for lovers</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/go-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/go-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo is for lovers</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/hugo-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/hugo-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new theme</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saying Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/saying-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/saying-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>I love being on vacation when there&amp;rsquo;s no cell phone reception.
I do NOT like when cell reception becomes available and all the missed contact attempts flood onto my phone. It feels like everybody wants a piece of me, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even officially back yet! I suppose I don&amp;rsquo;t haave to turn my phone on until I return home. Hmmm perhaps.
Even when you know it&amp;rsquo;s coming, you&amp;rsquo;re never ready to hear the words that your friend has passed away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear First Diary</title>
      <link>https://kortni.ca/blog/dear-first-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 1992 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kortni.ca/blog/dear-first-diary/</guid>
      <description>Dear Diary,
Today is the day that I first got you!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>